awebproxy.com 2015-03-15

# www.awebproxy.com - Free Anonymous USA Proxy Youtube

## Privacy Policy for awebproxy.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at: 

At awebproxy.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by awebproxy.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, awebproxy.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
awebproxy.com may use cookies. Visitors may be assigned what is known as a "session cookie" and/or a "csrf token". Both type of cookie are are encrypted and exist only temporarily. They have a short lifespan and expire quickly. Their main purpose is to deliver the user a customized experience while visiting the site, and to protect the server from harmful input when a user submits a new proxy to the list.

**Advertising Partners**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ......  
• Google Adsense

**Google Adsense / DoubleClick Cookie**  
The DoubleClick cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit awebproxy.com website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on awebproxy.com.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to awebproxy.com and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>

**Third-party Cookies**  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for the advertisements and links that appear on awebproxy.com that send directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

awebproxy.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Opt-Out**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. awebproxy.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Users may find more information about opting-out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising at the following URL: <http://www.aboutads.info/>

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
